Oh my gosh, this fits so bad. So stereotype. I would have not chosen them.
Hey everyone, it's the last video before a short winter break, so I thought let's have some fun today.
And in this video I did not decide what I'm going to wear, but my Patreon community did.
Shortly before Halloween, a lot of Halloween costumes were on sale from Fashion Nova and
I did a poll on Patreon and said, hey guys, what should I wear?
and these are the winners these are like four costumes I'm going to show you
today and I can already tell you I would have not chosen them but let's start with the first one
here we go
first outfit
okay let me check in the mirror
Wow, this is so stereotype. I mean, Halloween, cowgirl, I don't know.
Okay, actually it wasn't the first place in the poll because I did the poll and when I was ready
to order, because it was a two or three day poll on Patreon, the first two choices were already
sold out on Fashion Nova so this is actually number three in the poll and it
was just a few days before Halloween so everything was discounted a lot and it
also didn't arrive in time for Halloween so this is just the random hey look at
these funny outfits video which my patrons chose for me I don't know I would
never ever wear this out or on carnival or Halloween or whatever in general I'm
not a big fan of what's it called fringes these thingies here
probably I'm actually surprised that it fits this good it's size yeah it doesn't fit that good
because it's a bit too loose here but it's size small medium
but i mean the panties do fit really good and the top as well and this was also part of the outfit
that came with it yeah i know but i do have wait a sec
I do have a hat from one of the laughs I attended it's not gonna work with a ponytail but
here you go
real cowboy girl or not anyway
okay this is annoying me because it keeps sliding down it's slightly too big the fabric is
actually rather high quality for PVC fabric so it's really comfy. Rating this
outfit from 1 to 10 would be a... I mean in terms of fit an 8 but in terms of
would I wear it it would be like a 2.
Tell me in the comments if you would rate it differently.
Yeah.
Next one.
It's going to be...
The cheerleader outfit.
Another stereotype because when I think of American movies,
it's always the cheerleader girls that are popular or hot.
and it looks like it fits actually a 16 year old girl and I put it on
I think it's way too small and oh my gosh
it just looks so cheap I'm sorry but I mean compared to this the cowgirl was really high
quality when it comes to the fabrics and pieces because it was five pieces this is only two pieces
this is just so it looks just so cheap and short way too short it's rather built and i don't know
but since the 90s we do not wear our stuff on the hips anymore like this low but rather a bit higher
but i can't do it now because then otherwise everything would be on display and i am not
going to do it we'll see how YouTube is going to cope with my butt anyway so yeah
also the top is yeah I don't know what size it is it's extra small small maybe I should have opted for a small medium here too but a lot of stuff was sold out already as I said so okay now I need some pom-poms you know I always had the
impression that Halloween is like really when people dress up slutty in the US
and then I was told by friends no no no it's not like that but I was like in
every movie when there's a Halloween themed day or when there's Halloween
everyone is like bunny or a sexy devil or cowgirl cheerleader whatever so yeah
this also just proves me right that Fashion Nova sold all these outfits
retrospective the cowgirl was so much better so I have to rate this a 1
because I think it's worse than the cowgirl and yeah I don't know
on to the next outfit
and on to the next stereotype because it's going to be nurse outfit
it's so short
I mean the apron is kind of cute but I also have this headpiece.
Okay, first look in the mirror.
Oh my god, this fits so bad.
I don't even know what to say anymore.
Where do I wear this?
Like here?
like this
yeah the headpiece looks good like that
and
the stay ups
were not included here
so it feels
like an extra small
although the top part
feels like a medium
this is a 4 piece set
the dress, the apron, the shrug
and this hat thingy here
and again I have to say the fabric is rather decent quality
it's PVC that is not uncomfortable and not too hard
so it's actually quite comfortable
but yeah the fit is really weird and I feel like all the outfits run a bit small
and they also run...
a bit...
silly I have no idea what I should say to this this is I think the second place
in the voting on patreon about the costumes was a maid outfit I think I
would have preferred to made because it would have been black but rather sadly
was sold out and yeah this is I don't know I'm not going to look after anyone
wearing this I can tell you that and rating it from 1 to 10 the fit is really
bad I mean at least the other things did fit good but here the top part is like
can I go into like digits like 0.5 out of 10 I think that would be my rating here
okay I do have one other outfit I can see it finally in thanks to Mike who sent
this in addition to the outfits from the poll and I'm going to get changed
before I look in the mirror I can already say that this is way up my alley
I'm not half naked I'm not just some man's fantasy this is actually a costume
it should be an astronaut and look in the mirror okay the color combination is
wild I mean but other than that it's pretty fun
how does it like this like this so yeah probably like this oh I love that look
too yeah this is actually a detachable harness we have some arm warmers that
are detachable, the suit and this kind of glasses that comes with the costume.
The fit is horrible but yeah. I don't think they fit the costume at all.
This looks weird.
Turning around. So I really do think the glasses do not fit the outfit so off with them.
And yeah, the fabric is not the best quality, but I really love the pockets here.
It puts some snacks in there, for example.
And I think that it's really kind of a cool idea to do a harness out of this normal material,
fitting with the other decoration stuff here.
So yeah, this outfit is actually really cool.
And the costume, I would definitely wear this out for carnival or Halloween.
Maybe with a matching helmet.
Like an astronaut helmet or something.
That would be fun.
Thank you, Mike, you saved the day.
Because if I would have to rate this, rating it a...
I think it's a 6 out of 10.
Because it does fit, it's like a bit too short.
but it's a look, it's a costume, it's a catsuit. I love that. I think the arm warmers are a bit unnecessary.
I don't know, but the look is kind of cute with them.
And the details are really cool too. This is actually the best outfit of the video. If I
I would have like a ranking.
This would be number one, then the cowgirl.
I have to laugh about myself for putting cowgirl
on second place, but I mean, with the cheerleader
and the nurse, I think they're both like fifth place
or something.
I don't even know which was worse, the cheerleader
or the nurse.
What can I say?
It's okay, it's really okay.
But anyway, I had a lot of fun recording this video.
Thanks to everyone on Patreon who participated in the poll.
If you want to be included in these kind of actions,
head over to my Patreon and check it out.
There are a lot of behind the scenes materials,
exclusive photos and extra stuff there.
You can tell me your rating in the comments down below.
I hope you liked the video and had fun as well.
Give it a rewatch over the holidays
if you're bored or whatever.
and I'll see you next year basically.
Have a really nice time, really nice Christmas time,
fun holidays and a good time.
See ya, bye.